Finding Aid to the Alan Guttmacher Institute records SSC.MS.00720
Sophia Smith Collection
- Alan Guttmacher Institute records, 1960-2013; 2013-S-0064
  - Reports and Executive Summaries, undated (Box 15)
  - State Reproductive Health Monitor, 1990-1996 (Box 15)
  - The Guttmacher Report on Public Policy, 1997-2002 (Box 15)
  - Guttmacher Policy Review, undated (Box 15)
  - Guttmacher Policy Review, 2006-2013 (Box 16)
  - The Guttmacher Report on Public Policy, 1998-2005 (Box 16)
  - The Guttmacher Report on Public Policy, 1998-2002 (Box 16)
  - State Reproductive Health Monitor, 1990-1997 (Box 16)
  - Washington Memo, 1968-1997 (Box 17)
  - Family Planning Population Reporter, 1972-1981 (Box 17)
  - 11 Million Teenagers What Can Be Done About the Epidemic of Adolescent Pregnancies in the United States, 1976 (Box 18)
  - Abortion 1974-1975 Need and Services in the United States, Each State and Metropolitan Area (Box 18)
  - Abortion 1977-1979 Need and Services in the United States, Each State and Metropolitan Area (Box 18)
  - Abortion Services in the United States, Each State and Metropolitan Area, 1979-1980 (Box 18)
  - Abortions and the Poor: Private Morality, Public Responsibility, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Adolescentes de Hoje, Pais do Amanha Brasil, undated (Box 18)
  - Adolescentes de Hoy Padres del Manana Columbia, undated (Box 18)
  - Adolescentes de Hoy Padres del Manana Peru, undated (Box 18)
  - Adolescentes de Hoy, Padres del Manana Un Perfil de las Americas, undated (Box 18)
  - Characteristics of Patients Served by US Family Planning Clinics in 1981, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Contraceptive Services for Adolescents: United States Each State and County, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Data and Analyses for 1973 Revision of DHEW Five-Year Plan for Family Planning Services (Box 18)
  - Data and Analyses for 1975 Revision of DHEW Five-Year Plan for Family Planning Services (Box 18)
  - Data and Analyses for 1977 Revision of DHEW Five-Year Plan for Family Planning Services (Box 18)
  - Data and Analyses for 1978 Revision of DHEW Five-Year Plan for Family Planning Services (Box 18)
  - Data and Analyses for 1979 Revision of DHEW Five-Year Plan for Family Planning Services (Box 18)
  - Directory of Providers of Family Planning and Abortion Services, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Family Planning and Analysis of Laws and Policies in the United States, 1971 (Box 18)
  - Family Planning and Rural Poverty, 1967 (Box 18)
  - Family Planning Medicaid and the Private Physician, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Family Planning Services in the United States, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Health Care Reform A Unique Opportunity to Provide Balance and Equity to the Provision of Reproductive Health Services, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Induced Abortion a World Review 1990 Supplement (Box 18)
  - Informing Social Change, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Need for Subsidized Family Planning Services: United States, Each State and County, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Need for Subsidized Family Planning Services: United States, Each State and County, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Need for Subsidized Family Planning Services: United States, Each State and County, 1971 (Box 18)
  - Our Daughters' Decisions The Conflict in State Law on Abortion and Other Issues, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Prenatal Care In the United States A State and County Inventory, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Provisional Estimates of Abortion Need and Services In the Year Following the 1973 Supreme Court Decisions US Each state…, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Risk and Responsibility: Teaching Sex Education in America's Schools Today, 1989 (Box 18)
  - RU486 Science and Politics, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Rural Family Planning Programs, 1967 (Box 18)
  - Safe and Legal: 10 Years' Experience with Legal Abortion in New York State, 1980 (Box 18)
  - State Implementation of the Medicaid Eligibility Expansions for Pregnant Women, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Teenage Pregnancy in the United States The Scope of the Problem and State Responses, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Teenage Pregnancy the Problem that Hasn't Gone Away, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Testing Positive: Sexually Transmitted Disease and the Public Health Response, 1993 (Box 18)
  - The Chicago Area Plan for Development of a Coordinated Family Planning Program, 1971 (Box 18)
  - The Institute's Future III-VI Long Range Plans for the Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1981-1992, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Today's Adolescents Tomorrows Parents A Portrait of the Americas, undated (Box 18)
  - When the Occasional Wisdom is Wrong A Reexamination of the Role of Abortion as an Issue in Federal Elections, 1974-1986, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Women at Risk of Unintended Pregnancy 1990 Estimates, 1993 (Box 18)
  - A World Review, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Abortion Services in the United States, Each State and Metropolitan Area, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Abortion Services in the United States, Each State and Metropolitan Area, 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Barriers to Contraceptive Services, 1987 (Box 19)
  - Blessed Events and the Bottom Line: Financing Maternity Care in the United States, 1987 (Box 19)
  - Current Functioning and Future Priorities in Family Planning Services Delivery, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Current Functioning and Future Priorities in Family Planning Services Delivery, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Data and Analyses for 1980 Revision of DHHS Five-Year Plan for Family Planning Services, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Factbook on Teenage Pregnancy Tables and References for Teenage Pregnancy: The Problem that Hasn't Gone away, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Family Planning and Planning Families and International Comparison, 1987 (Box 19)
  - Making Choices Evaluating the Health Risks and Benefits of Birth Control Methods, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Organized Family Planning Services in the United States 1981-1983, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Sex Education and AIDS Education in the Schools: A Survey of State Policies, Curricula and Program Activities, undated (Box 19)
  - Teenage Pregnancy in Industrialized Countries, 1986 (Box 19)
  - The Financing of Maternity Care In the United States, 1987 (Box 19)
  - The Institute's Future IX, 1999 (Box 19)
  - USAID/ IFPP Lawsuit, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Women at Risk, 1987 (Box 19)
  - A World Review, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Abortion in Women's Lives, 2006 (Box 20)
  - Contraceptive Needs and Services with Selected Articles, 1995 (Box 20)
  - Cost to Employer Health Plans of Covering Contraceptives Summary, Methodology and Background, 1998 (Box 20)
  - Data and Analyses for 1976 Revision of DHEW Five-year Plan for Family Planning Services, undated (Box 20)
  - Family Planning Annual Report 2002 Summary Part 2, 2003 (Box 20)
  - Family Planning in New Hampshire Directions for 1980, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Pregnancy, Contraception and Family Planning Services in Industrialized Countries, 1989, undated (Box 20)
  - Prenatal Care In the United States A State and County Inventory Volume I and II, 1989, undated (Box 20)
  - Preventing Pregnancy, Protecting Health: A New Look at Birth Control Choices in the United States, 1991 (Box 20)
  - Preventing Unsafe Abortion and its Consequences Priorities for Research and Action, 2006, undated (Box 20)
  - Research Papers Medicaid Funding of Organized Family Planning Services, 1981 (Box 20)
  - The Demographic Evaluation of Domestic Family Planning Programs, 1975 (Box 20)
  - The Need, Availability and Financing of Reproductive Health Services, 1989 (Box 20)
  - The Politics of Blame: Family Planning, Abortion and the Poor, 1995 (Box 20)
  - Title X at 25 Balancing National Family Planning Needs with State Flexibility, 1996 (Box 20)
  - Uneven and Unequal Insurance Coverage and Reproductive Health Services, undated (Box 20)
  - Abortion in Kenya Factsheet, 2013, undated (Box 20)
  - Perspectives on Sexual and Reproductive Health, Vol. 45, No. 3 (2013) (Box 20)
  - Adding It Up: The Need for and Cost of Maternal and Newborn Care – Estimates for 2012, undated (Box 20)
  - Guttmacher Policy Review, Vol. 16, No. 3 (2013) (Box 20)
  - Incidence and Complications of Unsafe Abortions in Kenya, 2013 (Box 20)